<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<fpdoc-descriptions>
<package name="fpGUI">

<module name="fpg_popupwindow">
<short>Defines a popup window widget</short>
<descr><printshort id="fpg_popupwindow"/>. This class is not normally used directly, but well known
descendants are <link id="#fpgui.fpg_menu.TfpgPopupMenu">TfpgPopupMenu</link> and the popup window
that appears when the button on a ComboBox is clicked.</descr>

<element name="TfpgPopupWindow.PopupWidget">
<short>Indicates the widget that last displayed the popup window</short>
<descr><p>When querying the value of <var>PopupWidget</var>, note that it could be nil, or
contain a reference to a widget. If the value is not nil, it indicates the
widget that called the <link id="TfpgPopupWindow.ShowAt">ShowAt(widget, x, y)</link> method to display the popup window.</p>
<p>An example of where this is very useful is with the <var>TfpgPopupMenu</var> widget - which
is a descendant of <var>TfpgPopupWindow</var>. The OnClick event handler of the menu item
can query the PopupWidget to know which widget displayed the menu. Often used where
popup menus are shared between multiple widgets.</p>
</descr>
<seealso>
<link id="#fpgui.fpg_menu.TfpgPopupMenu">TfpgPopupMenu</link>
</seealso>
</element>


<element name="TfpgPopupWindow.ShowAt">
<short>When called, will display the popup window at location (x,y)</short>
<descr><printshort id="TfpgPopupWindow.ShowAt"/>.</descr>
</element>

<element name="TfpgPopupWindow.ShowAt.AWidget">
<short>Specifies the widget that called the ShowAt() method. If ShowAt() without AWidget is called, then the X and Y coordinates are screen coordinates. No coordinate translation is done.</short>
</element>

<element name="TfpgPopupWindow.ShowAt.X">
<short>X coordinate where the popup window will display.</short>
</element>

<element name="TfpgPopupWindow.ShowAt.Y">
<short>Y coordinate where the popup window will display.</short>
</element>

<element name="TfpgPopupWindow.ShowAt.ACanAdjustPos">
<short>As the name suggests - do we allow the display position to be adjusted. eg: if x,y coordinate means the window will not fit on the desktop.</short>
</element>

</module>

</package>
</fpdoc-descriptions>
